tastyreview.com 2015-03-29

# Tasty Review

This privacy policy applies to your use of the TastyReview websites located at [www.TastyReview.com](http://www.tastyreview.com/), but not does apply to any third party sites that may be linked to them, or any relationships you may have with the business listed on the TastyReview Sites.

The terms " **we** ", " **us** ", and " **TastyReview** " refer to TastyReview.com. The terms " **you** " and " **your** " refer to you, as a user of any of the TastyReview Sites. The term " **personal information** " means information that you provide to us which personally identifies you to be contacted or identified, such as your name, phone number, email address, and any other data that is tied to such information.

BY USING THE TastyReview SITES, YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THESE TERMS, PLEASE DO NOT USE THE TastyReview SITES.

### **I. Information We Collect and How We Use It**

We use commercially reasonable efforts to ensure that the collection of personal information is limited to that which is necessary to fulfill the purposes identified below. If we use your information in a manner different than the purpose for which it is collected, then we will ask you for your consent prior to such use.

_Feedback._ If you contact us to provide feedback, register a complaint, or ask a question, we will record any personal information and other content that you provide in your communication so that we can effectively respond to your communication.

_Activity._ We record information relating to your use of the TastyReview Sites, such as the searches you undertake, the pages you view, your browser type, IP address, requested URL, referring URL, and timestamp information. We use this type of information to administer the TastyReview Sites and provide the highest possible level of service to you. We also use this information in the aggregate to perform statistical analyses of user behavior and characteristics in order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of the TastyReview Sites. You cannot be identified from this aggregate information. 

_Cookies._ We send cookies to your computer in order to uniquely indentify your browser and improve the quality of our service. The term " **cookies** " refers to small pieces of information that a website sends to your computer's hard drive while you are viewing the site. We may use both session cookies (which expire once you close your browser) and persistent cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them). Persistent cookies can be removed by following your browser help file directions. If you choose to disable cookies, some areas of the TastyReview Sites may not work properly or at all.

_Enforcement._ We may use the information we collect in connection with your use of the TastyReview Sites (including your personal information) in order to investigate, enforce, and apply our Terms of Service and Privacy Policy.

### **II. Transfer of Information**

We may share your personal information with our parent company, subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under a common control (collectively, " **Affiliates** ") that we may have now or in the future, in which case we will require them to honor this Privacy Policy. If another company acquires our company or our assets, that company will possess your personal information, and will assume the rights and obligations with respect to that information as described in this Privacy Policy.

We may disclose your personal information to third parties in a good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to (a) take action regarding suspected illegal activities; (b) enforce or apply our Terms of Service and Privacy Policy; (c) comply with legal process, such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order; or (d) protect our rights, reputation, and property, or that of our users, affiliates, or the public. Please note that we are not required to question or contest the validity of any search warrant, subpoena or other similar governmental request that we receive.

We may disclose information in the aggregate to third parties relating to user behavior in connection with actual or prospective business relationship with those third parties, such as advertisers and content distributors. For example, we may disclose the number of users that have been exposed to, or clicked on, advertising banners.

We use third party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the TastyReview Sites. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [_click here_](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 

### **III. Links**

The TastyReview Sites may contain links to third party websites to which we have no affiliation. Except as set forth herein, we do not share your personal information with those third parties, and are not responsible for their privacy practices. We suggest you read the privacy policies on all such third party websites.

### **IV. Security**

If you have any questions about the security on the TastyReview Sites, please contact us. Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that your personal information will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy.

_You hereby acknowledge that TastyReview is not responsible for any intercepted information sent via the internet, and you hereby release us from any and all claims arising out of or related to the use of intercepted information in any unauthorized manner._

### **V. E-mails and Opt-out**

You may opt-out of receiving personal messages from specific users. In addition, you may opt-out of receiving notifications from us by changing your notification settings under the "Account" tab after you log on to a TastyReview Site. Unregistered users who receive e-mails from us may also opt-out of receiving further e-mails by following the instructions contained in our e-mails. Despite your indicated e-mail preferences, we may send you notices of any updates to our Terms of Use or Privacy Policy.

### **VI. Terms and Modifications to this Privacy Policy**

We may modify this Privacy Policy at any time, and we will post any new versions on this page. If we make any material changes in the way we use your personal information, we will notify you by sending an e-mail to the last e-mail address you provided to us and/or by prominently posting notice of the changes on our website. Any such changes will be effective upon the earlier of thirty (30) calendar days following our dispatch of an e-mail notice to you or thirty (30) calendar days following our posting of notice of the changes on our website. These changes will be effective immediately for new users of the TastyReview Sites. Please note that at all times you are responsible for updating your personal information to provide us with your most current e-mail address. In the event that the last e-mail you have provided us is not valid, or for any reason is not capable of delivering to you the notice described above, our dispatch of the e-mail containing such notice will nonetheless constitute effective notice of the changes described in the notice. In any event, changes to this Privacy Policy may affect our use of personal information that you provided us prior to our notification to you of the changes. If you do not wish to permit changes in our use of your personal information, you must notify us prior to the effective date of the changes. Continued use of the TastyReview Sites following notice of such changes shall indicate your acknowledgement of such changes and agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes.

### **VII. Dispute Resolution**

If you believe that TastyReview has not adhered to this Privacy Policy you may write to the TastyReview Privacy Officer at the following address:

_TastyReview, Inc. Privacy Officer  
TastyReview.com   
PO BOX 15014   
BOSTON MA 02215   
Email to: Support@TastyReview.com _

In your letter, please describe in as much detail as possible ways in which you believe the Privacy Policy has not been complied with. We will investigate your complaint promptly.

### **VIII. Contacting the Website and Access to Your Personal Information**

Upon written request, subject to certain exceptions, TastyReview will inform you of the existence, use, and disclosure of your personal information and will give you access to that information. Access requests should be sent to our Privacy Officer, using the contact information above. 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the privacy practices of this website, or if you want to exercise any of the rights that you are given under this Privacy Policy, you can contact us using the contact information listed above.
